[right hand] reach toward dominoes on the table | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp a domino | [right hand] grasp another domino | [ego] stay still
[left hand] lift a domino upward | [right hand] lift a domino upward | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place a domino upright on the table | [right hand] place a domino upright on the table | [ego] stay still
[left hand] adjust a domino into a vertical stack | [right hand] adjust a domino into a vertical stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] pick up a domino and place it beside the stack | [right hand] hover near the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up a domino and place it into the stack | [left hand] hover near the stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] pick up a domino and place it into the stack | [right hand] hover near the stack | [ego] stay still
[both hands] hover near the completed domino stack | [ego] stay still